{
  "quizs": [
    {
      "question": "Odpowiedz A jest poprawna (indeksy od 0)",
      "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Odpowiedz B jest poprawna (indeksy od 0)",
      "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "points": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Odpowiedz C jest poprawna (indeksy od 0)",
      "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "Odpowiedz A jest poprawna (indeksy od 0)",
      "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "points": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Odpowiedz B jest poprawna (indeksy od 0)",
      "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Odpowiedz C jest poprawna (indeksy od 0)",
      "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "points": 5
    },
    {
      "question": "Odpowiedz A jest poprawna (indeksy od 0)",
      "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
      "correctAnswer": 0,
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Odpowiedz B jest poprawna (indeksy od 0)",
      "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
      "correctAnswer": 1,
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Odpowiedz C jest poprawna (indeksy od 0)",
      "answers": ["A", "B", "C", "D"],
      "correctAnswer": 2,
      "points": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "AAA",
      "answers": ["A", "V", "v", "v"],
      "points": 1,
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "AAA",
      "answers": ["A", "V", "v", "v"],
      "points": 1,
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "AAA",
      "answers": ["A", "V", "v", "v"],
      "points": 1,
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "AAABC",
      "answers": ["A", "V", "v", "v"],
      "points": 1,
      "correctAnswer": 0
    }
  ]
}
